daminion.net 2017-12-21

# Privacy Policy | Daminion Software | Archive Server for Digital Assets

### Introduction

We respect your right to privacy. We will never sell your name to a third party without your express consent.

Because we feel your privacy is so important, we are providing this page to describe when and how we collect and use your information.

### Information collection

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information") or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you register for an online service or when you provide information in connection with an online transaction.

When you order, we ask you for your name, e-mail address, shipping and billing addresses, telephone number, and credit card information. When you enter a contest or other promotional event, we may ask for your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and your time spent at our sites, and to gather broad demographic information. This allows us to see which parts of our sites users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means, for instance, that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will remain anonymous. We do not use it for any other puposes. When a user submits personal information, it is kept on a private server not accessible from the Internet. This prevents any malicious use of your information.

### Use of personal information

Daminion Software may share non-personal, summary information regarding its customers with partners or other third parties. However, for partners or third parties under contract with Daminion Software, any individual customer information provided shall be used only to perform or complete a necessary transaction or function related to the customer's purchase. These transactions or functions shall be in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy Statement. PicaJet.com will not share any individual customer information outside of the contracted partners and third parties mentioned above, without first receiving the individual's prior written approval. In short, Daminion Software does not sell registrant information to lists. In some cases,Daminion Software may use a visitor's personal information to understand overall patterns for site usage, to contact the user for clarification on inaccurate information, or to follow up on a customer service issue. Personal information may include name, address, telephone number, etc.

### Opt-Our policy

When a visitor registers, the visitor will be given the opportunity to select whether or not to be included in the Daminion Software mailing list. Inclusion on the mailing list may entitle the user to receive information or updates about special offers, programs, new products and/or services. Choosing not to register means the user will not be able to receive these benefits or this information.

### Online purchase

When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server, which increases the security of each transaction. Our secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, we take steps to protect the customer data we collect from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Credit card numbers are used only for processing payments the user requests through this service and are not retained for other purposes. When you submit an order on-line, your credit card number is submitted to the credit institution for normal, routine processing. Daminion Software does not collect your personal credit history information and does not share credit or credit card information with other third parties unless compelled by law or a court order to do so.

### Links to other sites

This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Daminion Software is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web Sites as well as any information they might collect, even though our name or logo may appear on those sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the Privacy Statements of each and every Web site that you visit, as the privacy policy of those sites may differ from ours. Our Privacy Statement applies solely to http://www.daminion.net/

### Cookies

Netscape provides the following explanation: "A cookie is a small bit of information that a web site stores on your computer. When you revisit the web site, your browser sends the information back to the site." Please visit http://home.netscape.com/.../cookies.html for further explanation of cookies.

 A cookie does not contain any Personal Information. The use of cookies are not required to use this web, but it does enable Daminion Software to build a better web site by recording how and when guests use our site and to better serve you when you return to our site. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, but if you do, you might not be able to take full advantage of our site.

* * *

To help us improve our privacy policies, please give us your feedback, comments and suggestions.
